Jamal Gordon

4931 Jamesville Rd, Montauk, NY 30456 jgordon@mail.com (475) 293-8938

Highly skilled finance manager with extensive background in the real estate industry. Experienced with the latest techniques and software tools for cash, credit, and insurance management. Proven ability to help organizations consistently achieve their revenue goals.

Key Skills

- Budgeting
- Account reconciliation
- Cash flow projection
- Market analysis
- ♦ Zoho
- ♦ Xero
- Expensify
- ♦ Fresh Books

Professional Experience

Finance Manager

Town & Country Rea! Estate, Montauk, NY I December 2010 - Present

- Assist homeowners with loan modification documents and procedures
- Develop training materials for new hires
- Set up vendor payments, administer bank accounts, and manage account reconciliation
- Perform regular spending analysis and identify areas for improvement

Finance Officer

Stone Ridge Development, Albany, NY } June 2004 - December 2010

- Developed annual budget and standard procedures for day-to-day operations
- Provided cash flow projections, account reconciliation, and market analysis
- Worked closely with development teams to assess viability of project proposals
- Exceeded revenue targets by over 50% during tenure

Education

Master's Degree in Finance

University Of Albany, Suny Albany, NY, September 2002 - June 2004

Bachelor's Degree in Economics

Farmingdale State College, Suny East Farmingdale, September 1998 - June 2002

Certifications

 Financial Modeling & Valuation Analyst, Corporate Finance Institute, 2015